[{"question": " six dollars, please.", "answer": " six? i just had it for one night. it\u0092s three.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " eight o\u0092clock is the cut-off and,  aww, it\u0092s 8:02.", "answer": " y'know in a weird way, you have too much power. look, you\u0092re gonna have to help me out here, \u0091cause i only have three.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": "  i can help with that.", "answer": " oh my god. richard?  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " wow! your lip went bald.  hey, thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " so, you look great.", "answer": " right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " no you do. you... just...", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " you\u0092ve got panties stuck to your leg.", "answer": "  that\u0092s because i-i was just grabbing some things out of the dryer, and it\u0092s static cling. or maybe it\u0092s just that god knew i\u0092d be running into you and saw an opportunity.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " it\u0092s good to see you.", "answer": " it\u0092s good to see you too.  opening credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " you see that guy? he\u0092s in classics now, but y'know as soon as we leave he\u0092s going straight to the porn.", "answer": " he\u0092s gonna go up to the counter with citizen kane, vertigo, and clockwork orgy.  this is nice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " i missed this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " me too.", "answer": " so, you wanna get a hamburger or something?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " oh, um, i don\u0092t know if that\u0092s a good idea.", "answer": " oh. look, just friends, i won\u0092t grope you. i promise.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " no, i just i think that it\u0092s too soon.", "answer": " no it\u0092s not too soon, i had lunch at a eleven.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " yeah, baby!", "answer": " what are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " making chocolate milk. do you want some?", "answer": " no thanks. i\u0092m 29.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": "  oh my god, i gotta go to work!", "answer": " oh sweetie, when do you think you\u0092re going to get off tonight?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " oh i don\u0092t know honey. it\u0092s gonna be really late.", "answer": " oh come on, not again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " i know. i\u0092m sorry. look, i\u0092ll make a deal with you all right? okay?", "answer": " hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " for every night that you\u0092re asleep before i get home from work...", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " i will wake you up in a way that\u0092s proved very popular in the past.", "answer": " now, if you need to stay late, i want to be supportive of that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " right.", "answer": "  hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": "  look at you. since when do you roller blade?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " oh! since tomorrow. i met this really cute guy in the park and he like y'know, jogs, and blades, and swims, and so y'know we made a deal that\u0092s he\u0092s going to teach me all sorts of jock stuff.", "answer": " and what are you going to do for him?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " i\u0092m going to let him.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " cool.", "answer": "  morning.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " somebody got in late last night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " when did this happen?", "answer": " oh, um, around 8:02. we ah, talked for a little while, and then um, we went out for an innocent burger.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " oh, there\u0092s no such thing as an innocent burger.", "answer": " so, are you gonna see him again?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " tomorrow night.", "answer": " monica, what are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " well, she spent the last six months getting over him, and now she\u0092s celebrating that by going on a date with him.", "answer": " it\u0092s not a date, okay. i\u0092m just gonna teach him how to make lasagne for some pot luck dinner he has.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " well, you might wanna make a little extra, y'know you\u0092ll probably be hungry after the sex.", "answer": " we\u0092re not gonna have sex! okay, nothing\u0092s changed here. he still doesn\u0092t want children and i still do, so that\u0092s why we\u0092re just gonna be friends.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " do you have any ice?", "answer": " check the freezer. if there\u0092s none in there, then we\u0092re probably out. are you just getting in from work? it\u0092s late.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " yeah, i know. i had the greatest day though, i got to sit in on the meeting with the reps from calvin klien. i told my boss i liked this line of lingerie, she ordered a ton of it. how was your day?", "answer": " i discovered i\u0092m able to count all of my teeth using just my tongue.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " hmm.  umm, why do you have a copy of the shining in your freezer?", "answer": " oh, i was reading it last night, and i got scared, so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " but ah, you\u0092re safe from it if it\u0092s in the freezer?", "answer": " well, safer. y'know, i mean i never start reading the shining, without making sure we\u0092ve got plenty of room in the freezer, y'know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " how often do you read it?", "answer": " haven\u0092t you ever read the same book over and over again?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " well, umm, i guess i read little women more than once. but i mean that\u0092s a classic, what\u0092s so great about the shining?", "answer": " the question should be rach, what is not so great about the shining. okay? and the answer would be: nothing. all right? this is like the scariest book ever. i bet it\u0092s way better than that classic of yours.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " okay. ah, well we\u0092ll just see about that, okay. i will read the shining,  and you will read little women.", "answer": " all right, you got it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " all right.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " ah, now rach, these ah, these little women.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " how little are they? i mean, are they like scary little?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " um, chandler, ross, this is robert.", "answer": " oh, hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": "  you\u0092ve have lipstick right here . that\u0092s okay, it\u0092s mine, we just kissed.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": "  so ah, isn\u0092t a bit cold out for shorts?", "answer": " well, i\u0092m from california.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": "  i\u0092m up! i\u0092m up, i\u0092ve gotten up now! anybody ah, want anything?", "answer": " i\u0092ll have coffee.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " yeah, me too.", "answer": " yeah, make that three.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " okay ross, why don\u0092t you come with me?", "answer": " okay.   what ah, what is the matter with you? what\u0092s going on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " robert\u0092s coming out.", "answer": " what, what do you mean, what? is he gay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " no. he.....he\u0092s coming out of his shorts.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " the man is showing brain.", "answer": " are you sure?  hold on.  i\u0092m sorry you guys, that was a coffee and a....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " coffee.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " we could write it down for you?", "answer": " no, no, that won\u0092t be ah, that won\u0092t be necessary", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": "  wellll?", "answer": " yeah, yeah, yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " what do we do? what do we do?", "answer": " well, i suppose we just try to not look directly at it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " so when people complement me on my cooking should i, what do i say?", "answer": " you say \u0091thank you very much,\u0092 and then you buy me something pretty. come on, we\u0092re gonna put are hands in this bowl, and we\u0092re gonna start squishing the tomatoes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " ew, this feels very weird.", "answer": " you touch people\u0092s eyeballs every day and this feels weird.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " yeah, well, sure i touch them, but i spent years learning not to squish them.  that\u0092s my hand.", "answer": " oops.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " gotta keep squishing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " tomatoes are squishing.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " op.", "answer": " oh, gosh, you got some on your shirt.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " hold on a second, just put a little club soda on it  and it should umm, be.....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " umm, you\u0092ve got some on your pants.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " these little women. wow!", "answer": " your liking it, huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " oh yeah! amy just burned jo\u0092s manuscript. i don\u0092t see how he could ever forgive her.", "answer": " umm, jo\u0092s a girl, it\u0092s short for josephine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " but jo\u0092s got a crush on laurie.  oh. you mean it\u0092s like a girl-girl thing? \u0091cause that is the one thing missing from the shining.", "answer": " no, actually laurie\u0092s a boy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " hey! how\u0092d the ah, basketball go?", "answer": " oh, okay, i learned how to shoot a lay-up, a foul shot, and a twenty-three pointer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " you mean a three pointer?", "answer": " oh, i get more because i\u0092m dainty.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " so um, is there a phone here, i can check my messages?", "answer": " yeah, in the back. you want a quarter?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": "  what are you doing?  get back over on your side of the...  hello!!  hi, i\u0092m joey, we haven\u0092t met.", "answer": " ah, good to meet you. robert.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " what?  what? you guys, what is going on? you not like robert?  why are you laughing?!", "answer": " calm down. there\u0092s no reason to get testy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " you guys!! come on!", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry, i\u0092m sorry, it just seems that robert isn\u0092t as concealed in the shorts area, as ah, one may have hoped.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " what do you mean?", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey robert, could you ah, ha, pass me those cookies?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " you really sure?", "answer": " i\u0092ll call you back.  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " so we can be friends who sleep together.", "answer": " absolutely, this will just be something we do, like racquetball.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " sounds smart and healthy to me. so um, just out of curiosity, um, do you currently have any other racquetball buddies?", "answer": " just your dad.  although that\u0092s actually racquetball. you know i-i do have a blind date with my sister\u0092s neighbour next tuesday.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " you want me to cancel it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " no!  no!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " \u0091cause if you do that means you\u0092d be cancelling it for me, and we\u0092re just friends.", "answer": " exactly.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey. ooh! don\u0092t sit down!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " you ready to go to the batting cage?", "answer": " yeah. and, first here\u0092s a gift.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " oh! wow! hey!", "answer": " stretchy pants! why, those are the greatest things in the world! if i were you i would wear them every day, every day!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " jeez, thank you really that is so nice. but um, to be honest, i don\u0092t think i can wear these, they\u0092re so tight, i feel like i\u0092m on display. i\u0092m sorry.", "answer": " that\u0092s all right, that\u0092s well, i figured....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!  how\u0092s it going?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " good.", "answer": " hey, rach, how you doing with the shining?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " oh, danny just went into room 217.", "answer": " oooh, the next part\u0092s the best, when that dead lady in the bathtub...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " oh, no, meh-nah-nah-nah, come on you\u0092re gonna ruin it!", "answer": " all right i\u0092ll talk in code.  remember when the kid sees those two blanks in the hallway?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " hmmm, that\u0092s very cool.", "answer": " oh, all blank, and no blank, make\u0092s blank a blank blank. oh no-no-no, no, the end when jack almost kills them all with that blank, but then at last second they get away. aww!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " joey! i can\u0092t believe you just did that!", "answer": " i can\u0092t believe she cracked your code!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " all right, okay, laurie proposes to jo, and she says no, even though she\u0092s still in love with him, and then he ends up marring amy.", "answer": " hey! mine was by accident! all right, the boiler explodes and destroys the hotel, and kills the dad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " beth, beth dies?", "answer": " um-hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " is that true? if i keep reading is beth gonna die?", "answer": " no, beth doesn\u0092t die, she doesn\u0092t die. does she rachel?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " joey\u0092s asking if you\u0092ve just ruined the first book he\u0092s ever loved that didn\u0092t star jack nicholson?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " no. she doesn\u0092t die.", "answer": " then why would you say that?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " because, i wanted to hurt you.", "answer": "  oh, there they are! i-i dropped my keys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": "  oh my....", "answer": " got \u0091em.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": "  sorry. i\u0092m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " what are you smiling at?", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry, i was just thinking you\u0092re day could still pick up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " hello.", "answer": " i love this friend thing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " listen, robert\u0092s gonna be here any second so, will one of you just tell him?", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " please, right now, no, every time i see him it\u0092s like \u0091is it on the lose?\u0092 \u0091is it watching me?\u0092", "answer": " we can\u0092t tell him, you can\u0092t go up to a guy you barely know and talk about his.... stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": "  so are ready for the gym? they\u0092ve got this new rock climbing wall, we can spot each other.", "answer": " no, i can spot you from here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " okay, listen robert...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": "  hey, don\u0092t we have to...", "answer": " yeah, we got, um-hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " umm, i think you\u0092re really, really great...", "answer": " oh god! here we go again. why does this keep happening to me?  is it something i\u0092m putting out there? is this my fault? or am i just nuts?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " i-i-i-i-i don\u0092t know, i don\u0092t know what to say.", "answer": "   hey buddy, this is a family place, put the mouse back in the house.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " ow!", "answer": "  really?! well, it\u0092s just like everyone else\u0092s apartment. it\u0092s got rooms, walls, and ceilings.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " well, i just wanted to see where you lived. now, give me the tour.", "answer": " oh my god! oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " ah well, this is the living room.", "answer": " impressive.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " all right. this is the kitchen.", "answer": " oh, that\u0092s real pretty. wait a minute, don\u0092t i get to see the bedroom?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " the bedroom. well it\u0092s pretty much your typical...  bedroom.", "answer": " we\u0092re still on this side of the door.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " um-hmm.", "answer": " yeah, but i didn\u0092t get to see it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": "  so um, who was she?", "answer": " oh,  that was the blind date that i told you about, she called and switched it to today.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": "  did you like her? and i\u0092m just asking as a friend, because i am totally fine with this.", "answer": " well, you seem fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": "  okay, y'know what, i\u0092m not fine, i\u0092m not. i mean how can i be fine, hearing you come in with her, she wants to see your bedroom....  y'know what, what if we\u0092re friends who don\u0092t see other people?", "answer": " you mean like exclusive friends?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " why not?! i mean this has been the most amazing week. would it be so terrible? even if we were friends who lived together. or, maybe someday friends who stood up in front of their other friends, and vowed to be friends forever.", "answer": " wow. y'know we\u0092re back where we were. honey, i would love to do all that, but nothing\u0092s changed.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " that\u0092s not true, you don\u0092t have a moustache.", "answer": " okay, okay, one thing\u0092s changed. but we still want different things and we know how this is gonna end.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " y'know what, i\u0092ve got to walk out of here right now, \u0091cause getting over you is the hardest thing that i have ever had to do. i don\u0092t think i could do it again.", "answer": " i know i couldn\u0092t. so....", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " watch the thorns!", "answer": "  ow!! closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " beth is really, really sick.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " awwww.", "answer": " jo\u0092s there, but i don\u0092t think there\u0092s anything she could do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " joey?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " do you want to put the book in the freezer?", "answer": "  okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}]